so with that of course last one makes
others build on each other if you're not
watching these in order is a animal
share app which I was at a Vancouver
Claire know my classes I don't really
know why or why it's coming from it's
behind a few videos try to like get it
out of there I'll just hold my head
right there work someone that's not
strictly the pup sitting like that is it
an animal share app where you can have
comparative dog so somebody someone gets
my weekends or maybe where you're
sharing in if not the cost at least the
care of an animal and that we very
beneficial for someone like me I would
love to take one of my neighbor's dogs
for a walk because I'm home during the
day and I love dogs and I could totally
take it for a walk and that would be
free or cheap service for them and my
child I'm sure would love to drive
horses and so having a share in a horse
would be beneficial especially if part
of that came with knowledge and training
on how to take you to help take care of
it and so I just think there's yeah many
ways that we could share animals so that
we all don't need to have a horse and a
dog and a cat and we can all have access
to the amount of them what they bring to
our lives this pets bring a lot to our
lives
so Apple number 66 is an animal share
app